Guide to the Stanford University, Board of Trustees, Meeting Records SC1010
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records created prior to 2010, 1885-2009; Series 1
  - Supporting material, 1905-1976, 1998-2009; Subseries 3; 28 Linear Feet (56 boxes)
    - Earthquake damage report on Museum - notes on a blueprint of lower floor plan; Proposed installation of new rock crusher - report from W. F. Durand (M. E. Dept.); Power House location and operation - special report by W. F. Durand; Sale of land in Butte Co. to Southern Pacific Railway Co. (for Oroville and Nelson RR) - letters and documents, 1907 Oct 4 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - General Legislation and Standing Regulations of the Faculty - proof copy and related correspondence; Central Trust Co. - indemnity bond and related correspondence; Chas. G. Lathrop letter - purchse of rugs and furniture from Stanford residence; Ground lease of U. lands - proposed leases and related correspondence; San Luis Obispo lands - correspondence; Vina Ranch - letter and telegram from J. T. Graham on distillery report and ranch operations; Pacific Improvement Co. - correspondence re Guatemala-Champerico RR, 1907 Oct 25 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Student fees, including Law School- correspondence of Crothers, Jordan, A. T. Murray, C. H. Huberich; Pacific Improvement Co. - proxies and certificates; Alma Street extension over railroad - petition, map, and related correspondence; Phi Kappa Psi - lease and related correspondence; Fireman's Fund Ins. Co. - offer of property for sale in San Francisco; Notice of Completion of work on Gamma Phi Beta sorority house [photocopy]; Notice of Acceptance of work done on Delta Tau Delta house [photocopy], 1907 Dec 6 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Hetherington, Clark W. - correspondence re possible appointment at Stanford (athletics) and copy of his "Proposed School of Physical Education" and "The Organization and Administration of Athletics" and two printed articles; Roble Hall lights - petition from Roble Club and letter by Jordan; Transfer of bonds; Boyd Trust - correspondence and documents, 1908 Jan 10 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Financial report, 1908 Jan 31 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Vina distillery (Mandel as agent for) - correspondence; Pi Beta Phi sorority lease (17 Salvatierra St); Sigma Alpha Epsilon house - offer to sell to University (declined) and copy of 1901 lease, 1908 Feb 7 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Student parade of March 12 protesting liquor regulations: report by G. A. Clark, correspondence of Crothers; Sigma Alpha Epsilon house: lease and related correspondence; Financial report (monthly), 1908 Mar 27 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Committee of Engineers progress report on earthquake repairs; Liguor problem - report of committee on March 12 protest; Pi Beta Phi House Association - lease and agreeement with University; Lagunitas Sportsmen's Club - lease of shooting, hunting and fishing rights on Berry Ranch; Financial report (monthly), 1908 Apr 24 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Jewel Fund - correspondence and documents re its history and finances; Liquor Problem - report "The Customs as to the Use of Liquor in Stanford University" and correspondence; Elliott, O. L. request for lease of lot no. 1 in San Juan subdivision; Mortgage and correspondence re loan to Taft & Pennoyer of Oakland; Palo Alto land between county road and RR line, correspondence regarding; Vina Ranch - correspondence and lease to Soto Gun Club for shooting privileges; Sale of Metropolitan Street Railway Co. of N. Y. bonds, 1908 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Junior College Plan - correspondence of Jordan, Crothers; Men's Gymnasium - report by W. F. Snow, with map; Fire insurance; Miscellaneous: academic schedule, 1908 Commencement Program, identification of "obscene" anonymous letters, 1908 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Knight, Allen letter re sinking fund; University Club - correspondence and documents re construction of clubhouse in S. F; Society of California Pioneers, request for a loan; Stolz, Herbert's temporary absence as stenographer to Pres. Jordan; Elliott, O. L. letter to Jordan re entrance requirements; Cubberley, E. P. letter to Crothers re acquisition of education materials; Jordan appointment to International Commission of Fisheries, 1908 Jun 26 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Jordan, D. S. & Jesse, lease of 2 acres for cow pasture: correspondence and lease; Medical Department: organization of faculty & creation of Dept.; Hempl, George: lease and related correspondence (for San Juan Hill house); Lathrop, Charles G.: loan to Board of Trustees; Clark, A. B.: lease and related correspondence (for San Juan Hill house); Gold bonds of the Northern Railway of California, letters re sale; Lagunitas Water Co.: report by Charles D. Marx (re proposed reservoir in Marin County), 1908 Sep 11 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Vina Ranch, State Fair competition: letter and list of prize-winning cattle; Hoag & Lansdale: correspondence re laying sewer pipe on Univ. land in Menlo Park; Hoover, H. C. - appointed lecturer in Mining Engineering without pay, 1908 Sep 25 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Entrance requirements; Com. on Student Affairs; Revised lease forms; Lease of S. F. home property (Powell and California Streets), 1908 Oct 30 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Wine market surplus; Vina agency contract; Bond values; Automobiles on campus; Pacific Improvement Co. Trust; Crothers, George - attorneys fees, 1908 Oct 30 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Medical school - fees; Medical school - advertising; Pacific Improvement Co.; Bassett land lease; Palo Alto tree, 1908 Dec 4 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Endowment; Investments; Stanford seal; Cooper Medical College, 1908 Dec 4 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Discipline of undergraduates; Bolton, H. E. appointment; Earthquake, Comm. of Engineers, notice of completion of work; Law Department, 1908 Dec 18 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Gift of Mr. Thomas Beckwith's mound builders relics - correspondence re; Public Health Committee, letter re need of isolation hospital on campus; Mr. George J. Treator, gift of his shell collection - correspondence re; Jordan: letter urging backing of liquor ban bill in State Senate; W. F. Durand: Request for telephone system connecting the various departments; Thomas Arkle Clark as dean of undergraduates -Correspondence re; Pacific Improvement Company appointing Mr. J. H. Judge their New York representative -Correspondence re; Sale of Guatemala line by P. I. C. - Correspondence and clipping re; Dr. William F. Cheney, appointment to Med. School faculty - correspondence; Establishment of fellowship program - Jordan's letter re; Forestry - petition for instruction in, letter from W. R. Dudley; Request for a meeting room by Y.M.C.A. - correspondence re, 1909 Jan 29 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Vacancy on Board and appointment of J. Leroy Nickel - correspondence; Establishment of fellowship program - report of committee; Entrance requirements and possible elimination of 1st and 2nd year instruction: report and correspondence; Jordan on placement of bells in quadrangle; Chicago and Northwestern RR Co. bonds - correspondence; Hahnemann Medical College of the Pacific gold bonds - correspondence; Elliott, O. L. - lease and correspondence re changes; Jordan on proposed tower for Memorial Church; Jordan's request that an astronomy observatory be built on Frenchman's Lake; Telescope, request for - correspondence; Cooking gas for faculty houses - correspondence; Sale of syndicate lands in Madera County - correspondence; Bookplate for library authorized, with sketch; Isolation Hospital - correspondence re need of, negative decision on "Felt House", 1909 Mar 5 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - J. Leroy Nickel made Trustee; Fees for engineering courses; Re joining National Athletic Association; Establishment of a Division of Forestry recommended; Seismograph; Organization of the medical Department; Hotel del Monte: operating costs; Re widening of the Assembly Hall stage; Boyd estate; Tentative salary role and recommendations for faculty appointments and advancements, 1909 Mar 26 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Request for an automatic program clock; Request for bonus for Prof. Clark for his sobriety drive; Installation of gas for cooking purposes on campus; Faculty housing leases; Eating clubs building; Leasing of S. F. property, 1909 Apr 30 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Articles of Organization submitted by the Academic Council; Request that the Alumni President be made a member of the Board of Trustees; Establishment of Seismological Equipment at Stanford; Liquor bill passed; Trolley Road between campus and Palo Alto; Palo Alto property; Interest owed to Hubbard and Crocker by Galveston, Harrisburg and San Antonio RR; Organization of Stanford Alumni Association advisory board; Cooper Medical College; Palo Alto Railroad depot., 1909 May 28 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Liquor law; Cooper Medical College; Trolley., 1909 Jun 25 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Improvement Co: different business deals; Vina Ranch and Winery report; Marin Co. vs. Board of Trustees et al: settlement; Chaplain's report., 1909 Aug 2 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Opening of the Medical Department at Stanford; Vina Ranch and Winery report; Peninsular Railroad Co. agreement., 1909 Aug 27 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Vina Agency: Report of Finance Comm; West Memorial Lectures; YMCA room; Sale of Capital Traction Co. stock; Grape Growers: "Temperance vs. Prohibition" campaign; Penensular Railroad co; Representative for Harvard Inauguration; Hotel Del Monte., 1909 Sep 24 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Medical Dept. fees; T. B. Veblen: resignation; Rancho Tomales y Bolinas, Marin Co; Standard Coupler Company; Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Co; Memorial Church construction; Jordan request for leave; Trolley; T.W. Stanford: re-paintings., 1909 Oct 29 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Farmers and Mechanics Savings Bank; S. Prentiss Smith land lease; Pacific Grove-Pebble Beach Peninsula; Jewel Fund, 1909 Nov 26 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Lane Medical Library; Department of Education, Cubberley; West Memorial Lecture Fund; Cooper Medical College; Vina Ranch and Winery Report; Peninsular Railway Co; Pacific Telephone and Telegraph; University Club Building, San Francisco, lease., 1909 Dec 17 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Copies of documents re work done on campus houses; Home of O. L. Elliott, double house "C", A. B. Clark residence [copied 2007 at History San Jose] (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Land sale near Livermore; Professor Rolfe, Greek Department; West Memorial Lecture Fund; Vina Ranch and Winery Report., 1910 Jan 28 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Melville Best Anderson, first Emeritus Professor; West Memorial Lecture Fund; Pacific Improvement Co. Charles Lathrop resigns as representative; George Crothers elected; Dept. of Electrical Engineering; Candy Store - lease; Chicago and Northwestern Railway Co. Bonds; Farmers and Mechanics Savings Bank; Contagious diseases - Isolation hospital, 1910 Jan 29 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cooper Medical College; Stanford Union given permission to build on the university grounds; Registration Fee vs. Applicance Fee; Boyd Loan; Vina Ranch and Winery Report; Kappa Alpha Theta house lease; Thomas W. Stanford, Mar 25, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Medical Department; Woodside Golf Club use of Searsville Lake; Cooper Medical College and Lane Library; Guatemala Railroad Ferrocarril Occidental; Gas Company: campus connection; Street names; Cement Sidewalks - Alameda property; Space for Medical College in Museum, 1910 Apr 29 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Government Contracts to faculty; Dept. of Justice contract to faculty; West Memorial Lecture; Unversity Fellowships; Civil Engineering Department; Academic Council: Committee on University Organization recommendations; N.Y.C. rapid transit. Metropolitan Street Railway. New York Railways Co. Bonds; Guatemala Cintral RR Co; Pacific Improvement Co; Carbon Hill Coal Company, 1910 May 27 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - T.B. Sanatorium; Vina Agency; Land lease: Charles Lathrop; C.N. Ellingwood, Lane Medical Library lands., 1910 May 27 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Charles N. Ellinwood; Medical Dept.: Library Comm; Cooper Medical College; Trust Funds; McCoppin Ranch: sale of land; Guatemala Central RR. Purchase of Ocos RR. considered; Student fees; Beta Chi lease, Jun 17, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Purchase of Jarboe Library; Lane Medical Library Trust; Vina Rance and Winery report; T.W. Stanford, re-paintings; Cooper Medical College; Student Fees; Carnegie Foundation's report on Cooper Medical College, Aug 1, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Lane Medical Library; Tuition Fees; Vina Agency; Request of Alfred Sanford Blodget to buy horse pistols; Arboretum, proposed; Proposed eucalyptus farm; Treasurer's Report, 1910 Aug 26 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 500 limit; Chaplain's report; Ocos RR. bought by Guatemala Central RR Co; Vina Winery, Vina Ranch; Isolation hospital; Finance Comm. report on Univ. endowment, Oct 3, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Pacific Improvement Co; Vina Agency; Isolation hospital; Finance Comm. report on Univ. endowment, 1910 Oct 28 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Law School - Summer session; YWCA proposed boathouse; S.F. property; Vina Ranch and Distillery; Pacific Improvement C. increase number of directors; Cooper Medical College; Piping water to Calistoga Springs property; Southern Pacific Co. of New Mexico, first mortgage bonds, 1910 Nov 25 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Wm. R. Dudley, Emeritus Professor; Purchanse of Wm. R. Dudley library; Memorial Church reconstruction; Encina Club. petition to be allowed to smoke in Encina; S.F. property; Vina Ranch and Winery; Alder S. Blodget: refused horse pistols, 1911 Jan 6 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Lane Medical Library; Gun Club lease; Post office lease; S.F. property lease; Fuento Coal Co; Lake Lagunita: rules governing use of boats; Del Monte white sand business; Hotel Del Monte; Department head requisition forms; Lane Medical Library, 1911 Jan 27 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - T.W. Stanford: art gallery bequest and psychic investigation fund; Pacific Improvement Co. statement of assets, 1910; Pacific Improvement Co. liquidation proceedings; Hotel Del Monte; Chicago and Northwestern Railway Co; Beta Chi lease; S.F. property (corner of California and Powell Streets); Alameda Co. property deed, 1911 Feb 24 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Refused City of Palo Alto right of way for extension of Palo Alto Ave. (Alma St.) with copy of map [now classed as Map 541]; Education Dept. request for a one semester lab school; American Trotting Register Association Stock; Boating on Lake Lagunita; Academic Council, resolution of Tenure; M.F. Berdnikoff case; History Dept. purchase of books and mss; Herbert E. Bolton's resignation, 1911 Feb 24 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Natomas Consoliunitdated of California; Executive Comm. reprot on matter of opening unitdate of University; Wm. R. Dudley herbarium: gift; Dept of Medicine, budget; Re a pension for Dr. Matzke's widow; Am. Library Assoc. entertained at Stanford; Delta Chi Fraternity - house plans; Vina Ranch; Hotel Del Monte; Hartland Law - Mortgage; Jewel fund, 1911 Mar 31 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - West Memorial Lecture; Gymnasium fee; Lane Medical Library: to be a susidary of the Main Library; Medical Dept; Restoration of Paintings given by T. W. Stanford; Eating Clubs; Boyd Estate; Vina Agency; Memorial Church; West Memorial Lecture Fund; Academic Council: Comm. on graduate study; T. W. Stanford: art gallery and psychic research gift, 1911 Apr 28 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Delta Chi building; Pacific Improvement Co; Glee and Mandolin Club Eastern tour; Hotel Del Monte; Sly mortgage; O'Donnell injuction suit; Lane Medical Library, 1911 May 19 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Medical Department appointments; West Memorial Lecture fund; List of degree candiunitdates; List of spiritualist works in LSJU library; Tho. W. Stanford correspondence; Lane Medical Library building; Chaplain's report (D. Charles Gardner); Memorial Church: copy of letter from Salviati Company re mosaic work; Finance Comm. Report on Univ. Endowment; Univ. property lease (21 Salvatierra St.); New Palo Alto Depot; Pacific Improvement Co; Hotel Del Monte, 1911 Jun 30 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Mortgage on Kittredge property in S.F; Alexander Boyd Estate; Alaska Commercial Building mortgage; L. H. Sly, mortgage re property at California and Powell Streets, S.F., 1911 Jun 30 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Searsville Dam - Spring Valley Water Co. - Manzanita Water Co; Matyke, John E. - extension of his salary for his widow; Moore, Warran I; Lane Library - Rules concerning the use of books; Organ, Memorial Church; Buckley, Cornelius - mortgage on S.F. property; Vina Ranch report; Treasurer's statement; Real estate loans; Memorial Church (Report on steel frame); Lathrop gift to Medical School; Isolation hospital (includes sketch of proposed lot near Felt Lake); Lane Medical Library Construction, 1911 Aug 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - T. W. Stanford correspondence re gift; Gridley Ranch, includes blueprint; Memorial Church, work on pastor's study; Real estate loans; Agreement re power line crossing university land in Tehama and Butte Counties, 1911 Aug 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Barkan gift ot the Lane Library; Lathrop leases; Real estate loans; Vina Ranch report; Student Affairs Com. (Tubbings in Encina); Encina Hall - Rules and Regulations, Aug 25, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Del Monte Hotel; Vina Ranch report; Treasurer's report; Resolution formally defining boundaries of the campus; Stanford, Thomas W. gift of 20,000 pounds; Coleman, Borel, Meyer gift to medical library, 1911 Sep 29 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer's report; Hotel Del Monte report; Vina Ranch report; Power house construction; Real estate loans, 1911 Oct 27 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Stanford, Thomas W. gift to the library of books on spiritualism; Medical School appointments; Gridley Ranch, water rights on; Memorial Church, reconstruction;; Stanford, Thomas W. gift to the library; Gridley Ranch, water rights on; Memorial Church, reconstruction; Lane Library finances and construction; Treasurer's report; Vina Ranch report; Hotel Del Monte Report, 1911 Nov 24 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Memorial Church, reconstruction; Lane Library finances and construction; Treasurer's report; Vina Ranch report; Hotel Del Monte Report, 1911 Nov 24 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - West Memorial Lecture; Lane library stacks; Request to build one-room house by Boat House; Treasurer's statement; Hotel Del Monte report; Vina Ranch report; Eating Clubs, 1912 Jan 5 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Jewel Fund bookplate, correspondence with E. H. Blashfield; Memorial Church plumbing; Treasurer's report; Automobiles on campus; Stanford, Thomas W. psychical research, 1912 Jan 26 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Stanford, Thomas W. books on spiritualism; Treasurer's report; Boyd estate loan; Hopkins, Moses, memorial, 1912 Feb 23 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Mayfield street improvemtns; Memorial Church reconstruction - Lamb windows; Treasurer's report; Lane estate (Levi Cooper Lane) and Cooper hospital; Lathrop, Charles G. - resignation and rejection; Dodge, O. B. & Henry Lee Dodge Memorial Fund; Articles of Organization of Faculty - revision, May 29, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Stanford, T. W. books on spiritualism; Treasurer's report; "Henry Gibbons Jr. Library of Obstetrics and Gynecology"; Students' Guild Isolation Hospital, 1912 Apr 26 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - "Alumni Jordan Medical Scholarship"; Bernard, Henry M. scholarships; Stanford, Thomas W; Lane Library; Vina, Gridley and Palo Alto Ranches reports; Eating Clubs; Treasurer's report; Lane Medical Lecture Fund, 1912 May 31 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Real Estate loans; Vina Ranch report; Lane Hospital reserve fund; Lane Hospital, "plan for conduct of business"; Gray, George E. trustee; Holton fund, Luther J. for Lane Medical Library, 1912 Jun 28 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - [contents missing], Aug 1, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Lane Medical Library and hospital construction; County road through campus; Neilsen, Mrs. Kate Felton gift to Medical School; Yenington, Dr. H. H. gift to Medical School; Crothers, George E. gift to Law School; Vina Ranch report; Medical faculty meeting minutes; Treasurer's report; Gridley Ranch - James F. van Loben Sels bond, 1912 Aug 30 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Anderson, Frank B, elected trustee, 1912 Sep 4 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Har Dayal; Memorial Church temporary roof; Vina Ranch report; Treasurer's report; Phi Kappa Psi lease; Lane Hospital; Athletic grounds bleachers (stands); 21st Anniversary celebration; Alumni Association lease; Lane Hospital report; Alumni representation on the board, 1912 Sep 27 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - D. S. Jordan retirement; Vina Ranch report and additional ranch matters; Lane Hospital report; Alumni representation on the board; Pacific Improvement Co; Reid, Whitelaw - reason fot not being reelected; Crothers, George E. - reason for not being reelected, 1912 Oct 25 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Hoover, Herbert C. election to board; Newhall, W. Mayo election to board; Greene, Edward L. collection on Botany; Schmid, Rupert - sculptor; Memorial Church reconstruction - alter rail; West Memorial Lectures, publication of; Yolo Coutny tract; Lane Hospital (3 items); Popular Medical Lectures; Treasurer's report (2 items); Lease for new Trustee office in San Francisco, Nov 29, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Vina Ranch report; Treasurer's report; Gibbons, Jr., Henry Memorial Fund; Elkins, Felton B. - gift to Lane Hospital; Stetson, Miss Anna M. - gift of photographs of Greek statuary; Lathrop, Charles G. - gift; Reports from Clinical Committee and Lane Hospital, 1912 Nov 29 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Buckley, C. F. - loan; Memorial Church reconstruction, 1913 Jan 3 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Lane monthly report; Medical Faculty Minutes (2 items); General liability insurance; Vina Ranch salaries; Treasurer's report, 1913 Jan 31 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Pacific Improvement Co. business; Salviati and Co. - gift of Venetian glassware to Museum; General Education Board (John D. Rockefeller Fund) - funds requested of; Buckley mortgage, 1913 Jan 31 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Choir School; Medical faculty minutes and Lane Hospital report; Treasurer's report; Misc. matters - Vina and Gridley, 1913 Mar 7 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Medical faculty minutes and Lane Hospital report; Treasurer's report; Stanford Union; Rocky Mountain Coal and Iron Co; Water Commission - University stand on; Automobiles on Palm Drive, 1913 Mar 28 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Medical School - 5 year program; Buckley mortgage; Treasurer's report; Ranches - profit and loss statements; Street assessments; Barber, William Burton - loan fund; Kossuth fossil collection (Mrs. E.N. Stinson), 1913 Apr 25 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Law, Department of becomes Law School; Choir, Memorial Church - credit for; Medical Department and Lane Hospital; Branner, John C. - conditions for accepting presidency; Jordan, David Starr, chancellorship - whole of documentation on Jordan's retirement from presidency; Gymnasium, new and physical training; Sutro Library housed in Lane, 1913 May 23 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Endowment - difference between "founders" and "accrued" and other matters; Memorial Church - elimination of inscription; Alpha Tau Omega lease; Treasurer's report; Grounds Committee created; Special commitee on future academic policy; Hoover, Herbert C. gift to library, 1913 May 23 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Medical Department and Lane Hospital; Vina Ranch - state road through; Treasurer's report; Olmsted Brothers, location of stadium and other landscaping matters; Articles of Organization of the Faculty - changes in rules, 1913 Jun 27 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Lane Medical Library; Memorial Church Mosaics; Trasurer's report, 1913 Aug 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Dickey, W. J. scholarships; Faculty campus homes; Memorial Church - reconstruction, 1913 Aug 29 (Box 9, Folder 7)